Episode 20: Nonstandard
In third grade,
I beat up a cocky high schooler.
Handwriting
Fun to Learn
Arithmetic
Japanese
Even if he was older, cocky is still cocky.
He mocked me.
And when I feel mocked,
that's when the gong rings on the fight.
It wasn't that fun.
Trouncing a boring guy
was naturally boring, too.
Nice fight, boy!
What kind of woman is your type?
Who are you?
My boredom was about
to be flipped upside-down.
That was the feeling she gave me.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
It's time to unleash my technique!
Huh? Didn't you use it before?
However! I have no time
to explain my technique!
So there's only one thing I can say to you.
Don't stop!
Believe in me!
Okay! That's two, though!
Let's analyze our opponent's cards.
One is roots that emerge from the ground.
That one probably gains power and speed
the more it limits quantity and range.
Then there's Wooden Ball.
Each ball can attack once or twice,
and then it's expended.
They can remain airborne,
and I have to watch for delayed activation.
Then there's Cursed Bud.
That's probably what Fushiguro got hit with.
Guess you're out if even if one of those hits.
Though I want to believe that
means it can't fire too many.
Then there's Flower Field.
It looks like that relaxes you,
but its earlier wounds are throwing it off.
No need to be too wary of it.
Then there's that unleashed left arm...
And the possibility that
all of those are bluffs!
However, it doesn't matter what a
technique is if you don't let them activate it!
Even accounting for unexpected situations,
*Self-Proclaimed IQ 530,000
my IQ 530,000 mental CPU
produces only one conclusion:
Victory!
Because I'm not alone,
Brother!
Because you're here!
Toudou!
That's one down.
Oh, Toudou!
I see.
It's simple...
and therefore a troublesome technique.
Yeah.
My technique swaps my position
with my opponent's.
Boogie Woogie!
Toudou!
Shh! We'll end this before
it can get used to it.
By the way,
clapping my hands
is necessary to activate it!
Their builds are too different!
There's a big difference after they swap!
Is he swapping with me?
Or is he swapping with Sukuna's vessel?
Every time he claps, that split
decision makes my thoughts falter!
Oh, no! I can't...
...break out of this!
They're using that again!
Using Black Flash consecutively
isn't anything amazing.
\hNanami Kento, record holder for consecutive Black Flash uses, speaks\h
Though it is difficult to produce more than
twice in a row, or on a different day.
It doesn't matter if you land
the first by fluke or skill.
Once they land a Black Flash,
sorcerers temporarily enter
a state athletes call "the zone."
The manipulation of cursed energy
that they normally control consciously
becomes as natural as breathing.
There's a sense of omnipotence,
like everything else revolves around them...
That might be a good way to put it.
My record?
Four times.
I just got lucky.
Black Flash!
Brother,
I always get that premonition from you!
Black Flash!
Three in a row!
Don't get cocky!
Swapping positions?!
What I have to be wary of right now
is Sukuna's...
They didn't swap?!
Clapping my hands
doesn't necessarily mean
I'm activating my technique!
It's simple, but easy to fall for!
I'm getting that same premonition of
my boredom being turned upside-down!
Black Flash!
JUJUTSU KAISEN
It's attacking before each swap!
It's getting used to Toudou's technique!
But that Black Flash rush hurt it.
We can exorcise it!
Together!
This is the first time
I've ever been hurt so badly,
and despite that...
my delight in this battle isn't waning!
His technique reveal was full of lies!
He's able to swap two others, as well?!
Toudou!
He's protecting me!
Don't worry, Brother!
By seriously hardening my
body and cursed energy,
I'll easily repel these buds!
Are you sure?
T-Takada-chan?!
You remember Fushiguro-kun's injuries?
Of course I remember!
Those are the cursed buds about
to slam into me right now!
That's why I'm—
But remember,
Fushiguro-kun's buds had grown a little.
You think they grew by absorbing his blood?
That's not impossible.
But you're facing a cursed spirit.
What's most likely?
Cursed energy!
Happened in 0.01 seconds
He dispelled his cursed
energy right before impact?
He figured it out?!
The harder they defend with cursed energy,
the stronger those buds become!
Her next one's the national?
*National Handshake Event
I'll have to thank her then,
won't I?
Hey, special-grade cursed spirit,
I know you've realized
I didn't tell you everything then.
But there's one more thing
you should be thinking about:
what counts as a target for Boogie Woogie!
With what can I swap within
the range of my technique?
Only creatures?
Non!
My technique works on cursed corpses
and inanimate objects, too.
So the answer is...
Anything possessing cursed
energy above a certain level!
Hey, special-grade cursed spirit,
have you noticed?
We're back at that spot again.
This is where it lies waiting.
Maki-san's special-grade
cursed tool is in the riverbed.
The trees on its are face
are especially fragile.
The river?!
What did I swap places with?
Special-grade cursed tool,
Playful Cloud!
Even a blow from a special-grade cursed
tool imbued with my cursed energy
didn't completely take it down?
Plants don't generate cursed energy.
So my left arm steals the life from plants
and converts it to cursed energy.
But that never gets returned to me.
It all goes to this flower offering.
I didn't want to use this if I didn't have to.
Toudou!
Stay away, Brother!
Its cursed energy output is incredible!
But it will be easy for you
to avoid with your technique.
So what shall I do?
Domain Ex—
The veil!
I see.
I thought he sounded
pretty good without the amp,
but this old man is the amp himself.
His technique amplifies the tune he plays
and launches it as cursed energy.
He's a predictable mid-range fighter.
It's obvious he doesn't
want me getting close.
Let's make a wallet
full of that old man smell!
Roger that.
Nishimiya, you keep going, too,
and head to Shouko.
It's okay.
Mei-san has eyes on Miwa.
Thank God it didn't cut off my reception.
Guess that's only natural,
given the effect of the veil.
There's someone working with either
a curse user or curses at Jujutsu Tech.
Looks like he wasn't mistaken.
Huh?
I thought I cut you for sure.
A human?
A curse user?!
This is my problem...
This is nice, isn't it?
Juuzou made it for me.
Didn't you run into him earlier?
You're weak, so have the
sword hold your hand, too.
...he said.
Hey, what will you give me, lady?
Girls hate you, don't they?
You meet someone new,
and all you talk about is yourself.
I'll charge you for this.
What makes you think you're a good
enough listener to charge for it?
You guys!
Shut up! Stop picking fights
in moments like these!
Wow! So many girls!
I'm so popular!
Were you listening to me?
I'll cover you.
Be careful not to get hit in the crossfire.
You be careful not to hit me!
The veil lifted?!
For real?
It hasn't even been 30 minutes, has it?
Time to run!
What was his deal?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
I can see that slick coat rack now!
So...
Where should I start?
Huh?
Looks like this is as far as we go.
Huh? Gojou-sensei?!
Yuuji's on a much higher level than before.
I see! Aoi!
Of course he'd be a great match for Yuuji.
Looks like they're
fighting the special-grade,
but I shouldn't have to
worry about them now.
Which means my priority should be...
You.
Rack! Rack! Rack!
Don't kill him!
We have a lot to ask this guy.
Don't let him die on us.
Go on, treat him.
The guy near Utahime disappeared.
Guess he found a means to escape.
That just leaves that one?
One adept at running, too.
It's some distance from Yuuji.
Oh, well.
Guess I'll be a little rough.
Cursed Technique Amplification: Blue.
Cursed Technique Reversal: Red.
I'm withdrawing.
I'm not arrogant enough
to face Gojou Satoru.
Screw you!
What were you all trying to do here?!
Wait, Brother!
Why are you stopping me, Toudou?!
Don't take another step forward...
or you'll get caught in it.
Hollow...
Purple!
He's just as nonstandard as ever.
Now we can't tell if it was exorcised or not.
Ow! It hurts!
Quiet!
Yay!
That settles everything!
Or I guess it doesn't.
I wonder if Hanami's safe.
That's mission complete.
Juju Stroll
Salmon.
Q: Dog or cat?
Q: Are you a dog person or a cat person?
Dog?
No, maybe cat?
Wait, maybe dog if it's a big dog!
Q: Are you a dog person or a cat person?
Dog.
Dog, I think?
Q: Are you a dog person or a cat person?
What? I definitely prefer cats.
Salmon.
Q: Are you a dog person or a cat person?
The answer's obviously pandas!
You want me to kill you?! Huh?!
Everyone hates me,
don't they?
Well, there were only two choices.
Just leave him be.
Episode 21:
Jujutsu Koshien